DREW LICHTENSTEIN: Hi.
I'm Drew Lichtenstein.
And I'm a course producer at HarvardX.
And I'm here to talk to you about alternative navigation.
So alternate navigation in edX is this ability
to kind of add custom navigation to a course.
You can give a course a more custom look that sets it apart from other courses.
It's particularly nice, because, as I'm sure you realize,
edX is a very linear progression through the course material
if you just go through the outline or the horizontal bars that
are on the course pages.
And this alternative navigation lets learners see pathways
through the material that is not necessarily just from A to B.
So you can connect things that maybe are in section one to section eight
that otherwise you could just do with edX's default look.
It's also nice, because you can expose the entire course layout on a page.
So right now, default edX look, you can only see that on the outline.
But you could put course navigation on a single page
that shows where everything is.
Also, you can add your own aesthetic touch.
You no longer are restricted to using edX's icons,
so those default video assessment icons within your course navigation.
And so there's a lot of different things you can do with this.
The downside is that you've to make sure that whatever you put in
continues to play nice with edX.
You're putting in custom JavaScript, which means it could break at any time
when they update.
And so every time, you've got to kind of check.
Every couple weeks, make sure it's still there.
And also a lot of students who take edX courses
have taken previous edX courses.
So while edX's default navigation isn't great,
your students are probably used to using it, in which case
you want to make sure that the alternative navigation you put in
isn't confusing them.
I like to think of it more as supplemental navigation, that what
you're putting in isn't meant to replace edX,
but it is meant to provide an enhancement on what's already there.
So be sure you're clear about what you're showing
with your alternative navigation.
And that way, you can avoid student confusion.