COLIN FREDERICKS: Sometimes a few little tweaks are all
you need to make a course stand out.
Of course, you always want to have attention to detail.
AMY WOODGATE: A consistent page style and good proofreading
should, of course, be your first priority.
But once that's sorted, you can move on and put in some fun touches.
COLIN FREDERICKS: And those don't have to take forever to make an impact.
The examples we feature in this section are
quick to set up and provide diversity to your tool selection.
AMY WOODGATE: Many of those, if only I could do x or y, moments,
can be easily rectified through adding advance activity
types in global settings, and some require
creative use of existing functions.
COLIN FREDERICKS: Hacks.
We mean hacks.
AMY WOODGATE: Some of them are definitely hacks.
COLIN FREDERICKS: It's a nice way to ease yourself into course creativity.
These examples are short, pretty easy to set up--
AMY WOODGATE: And hopefully good fun to give you the development bug.
Enjoy.