DUSTIN TINGLEY: Hi.
My name's Dustin Tingley, and I'm a Professor
of Government at Harvard University.
I'm also the Deputy Vice Provost for Advances in Learning.
As part of that role, I run a team that embeds surveys in HarvardX courses.
Today, we're going to talk very briefly about some things
that we find to be very important that you probably already know, too,
but I just want to take a second to reinforce.
So one of the biggest things to remember about running surveys in a course
is that you only get one shot.
You can't go back to a survey respondent and say, hey,
can you please take this survey again because I'd
like to ask you this question slightly differently than the way you first
took it?
Doesn't work.
Pilot, pilot, pilot, pilot.
Have other people take the survey such that you can reduce the chance that you
want to change something later.
Have your friends take the survey, have your family take the survey,
have your boss take the survey, have other course
designers take the survey, et cetera.
It really, really helps.
Next, let's think about the quality of the data
that you're able to collect as a function of the amount of time
it takes a survey respondent to take your survey.
Anything longer than around 10 minutes, you're
probably facing a dramatic decline in the quality of data.
So when your boss comes to you and asks for hey,
let's add these 15 other questions onto the survey, remind them we can do that,
but that might decrease the quality of the data.
Then I think it's really important for us to think about the survey taker
and what their experience is.
Anything longer than 10 minutes, the quality of the data
is going to go down.
People get bored taking surveys that have lots and lots of text on a screen.
So how do you minimize that?
Keep the questions short and punchy.
Emphasize things using underlining or bold fonting
in order to really get the message across about what
it is that you're asking.
Furthermore, minimize the number of questions on a page.
Introduce page breaks between questions, such
that you're not confronting someone with a wall of text.
Branching questions are oftentimes used also to help reduce fatigue.
A branching question lets you ask, hey, here are two choices
and depending on how you answer amongst those,
I'm going to give you a slightly different question.
Branching questions help to reduce the amount of text
that needs to be on the page.
Finally, and this is a little pro trick, keep in mind
that many people might take your survey on a mobile phone.
So that means you need to check how your survey looks on a mobile phone.
That's really easy to do.
Take your survey on a mobile phone.
Finally, I just want to point out that I too often see
people in many different areas of industry and academia
running surveys and then rarely really analyzing the data.
It's as if they wanted the data, but not the insight
and the analysis that is possible from running one of these surveys.
So if you're asking your learners to take the time to answer your survey,
you should take the time to analyze it and think
about how you can make a better course using the information that they've
provided you.
Thank you very much.