COLIN FREDERICKS: Are we good?
Are we rolling?
Oh, OK.
We're rolling.
Awesome.
Why did we decide to do all the filming in one day?
AMY WOODGATE: I have no idea.
I'm shattered.
We meant to say thank you.
COLIN FREDERICKS: Oh yes.
Thank you.
Thank you to--
OK, let's see.
Fred, who's our video--
Fred, come over and say hi to people.
FRED: No, I don't want to be on camera.
COLIN FREDERICKS: OK, Fred's awesome.
He's our video editor.
He put all this stuff together.
He's great.
AMY WOODGATE: We've got our speakers.
COLIN FREDERICKS: Oh, yeah, yeah.
So Shilpa, Drew, Dustin, and Andrew, thank
you so much for helping out with this.
We couldn't have done this without you.
AMY WOODGATE: And thanks, 'Col'
COLIN FREDERICKS: Thank you.
Oh, and Shelley.
Shelley from MIT, who wrote some of the sections.
AMY WOODGATE: Absolutely.
COLIN FREDERICKS: And HarvardX for helping us
put all this together and for funding all this.
It's been wonderful.