AMY WOODGATE: Hello, and welcome to this course in advanced design
techniques in edX studio.
COLIN FREDERICKS: I'm Colin.
AMY WOODGATE: And I'm Amy.
COLIN FREDERICKS: And we're here to show you
some of the amazing things you can do in edX to improve your course environment.
AMY WOODGATE: Whether you've only got a few hours to top up skills,
or some serious dedicated time--
COLIN FREDERICKS: Probably over the weekend--
AMY WOODGATE: This course aims to provide straightforward, practical
guidance and implementation tips.
COLIN FREDERICKS: The goal is to improve your design skills
and make your next edX course really stand out.
AMY WOODGATE: You don't have to be a coding whiz to engage with this course.
Whilst a few sections do come with serious health warnings,
the vast majority are aimed at those generally familiar with the edX
tools, but keen to learn a bit more of the workings behind the scenes.
COLIN FREDERICKS: Where possible we've tried to show you each tool in action.
AMY WOODGATE: A bit of meta-learning, if you will.
COLIN FREDERICKS: On these pages you may be greeted full-on immersion style,
straight into the tool, to get familiar with how it works.
AMY WOODGATE: Hopefully you'll have as much fun going through the course,
as we've had building it.
Enjoy.