COLIN FREDERICKS: Considering your design philosophy
prior to building a course can save a lot of time in the long run.
AMY WOODGATE: We've all had those, oh, if only I
had done that thing earlier moments when creating courses.
So this section is designed to encourage good practice reflections
during the planning stage.
COLIN FREDERICKS: Prior to creating content on the platform.
AMY WOODGATE: This section's main focus is on features
that need careful consideration and justification at the design
stage as the implications for build can be vast
if not properly thought through.
COLIN FREDERICKS: These features are notoriously difficult
or time consuming to build, let alone edit once on the platform.
So the design planning stage is crucial.
AMY WOODGATE: However, these are also the features
often mooted at design sessions as something fun
or interestingly different.
COLIN FREDERICKS: In this section, we will not only provide you with the tools
to build these but also to say no and justify why.