COLIN FREDERICKS: So you've managed to cordon off an entire afternoon
to yourself just to work on your class.
AMY WOODGATE: No meetings, no interruptions.
Lucky you.
Now what?
COLIN FREDERICKS: Well, you could do something
where you need to comb through your entire course,
like converting all your images to figures,
things that add a professional touch.
AMY WOODGATE: You could do something that
requires a bit more planning, like writing a survey
or setting up learner cohorts.
COLIN FREDERICKS: You could also do something
that might require stretching your skills
and doing a little bit of troubleshooting,
like batch processing your course with Python.
AMY WOODGATE: We should get started before we run out of afternoon.
COLIN FREDERICKS: Oh, yeah.
[LAUGHS]