AMY WOODGATE: Quite a lot of this course focuses
on straightforward implementation and improved operating procedures.
COLIN FREDERICKS: This section is the hard stuff, and it needs to be that way.
AMY WOODGATE: Many of these longer projects require a massive upfront investment
in different areas, such as learning the code, setup requirements,
understanding specific nuances of the platform,
and last but not least, planning out the whole endeavor.
COLIN FREDERICKS: We're not trying to put you off using these features.
We just want you to understand that they are not easy or quick,
and they require a lot of careful thought and planning.
AMY WOODGATE: So the next time someone says--
COLIN FREDERICKS: I've got a great idea.
Let's make the course adaptive.
AMY WOODGATE: You at least will know what that actually
means for cost development and so can make a well-informed decision.