AMY WOODGATE: There are some improvements you just can't make in a few minutes.
COLIN FREDERICKS: Or in a day or a week.
There are things you need to do as a part
of your regular course-building practice.
AMY WOODGATE: For example, if you write clean HTML from the beginning,
you'll never have to clean it up.
COLIN FREDERICKS: And neither will the person who works on the course after you.
AMY WOODGATE: The goal is to do a hill of work now to avoid a mountain of work
later.
COLIN FREDERICKS: This section doesn't really have projects in the same way
that the others do.
AMY WOODGATE: Instead, we're going to propose some changes
to your workflow that will make you more efficient
or make your course more beautiful.
COLIN FREDERICKS: It's a lot of work to change how you do things,
but we promise these new approaches are definitely worth the effort.