Colin: This is a quick demo of the bridge for adaptivity in action.
I've got the course outline open here, and I'm
going to dive in to this particular section that you're indexing.
The page loads.
We've got a video on top of the professor,
and underneath it is our adaptive assignment.
The top left is the problem number.
I haven't done any so far, so it's just problem one.
The top right is the earned grade.
Here it actually has a number in it, because I've
done some related problems elsewhere in the course.
I'm going to read the question.
OK, I'm going to answer that, and I submit.
And I am correct.
Excellent.
So now I'm going to hit the Next button, and the bridge
read activity will give me another question.
Might be on the same topic or a related one or it could be a new question.
And I'll just go ahead and answer this one.
Good, OK, and I can check the answer just like any other EdX problem,
because it really is an EdX problem.
A little bit later on problem three, the more questions I answer
right, the higher my grade goes.
If I answer wrong, grade goes down.
You can see that this problem is going to be a bit harder than my last one.
When I'm happy with the grade for this assignment
or if I just run out of problems, I can move on to the next page.