SHILPA IDNANI: Hello, my name is Shilpa Idnani.
I am a program manager at the MIT Office of Open Learning.
Previously, I was at HarvardX, where I was an instructional technologist
and tasked with a wide variety of technical tasks across courses.
One of the things that I was often told to do
was to change the settings on a set of videos
or change the settings on every single assessment,
due to a procedural change, a process change, or an organizational change.
Now you want to change something very precise,
something like video downloading, video transcription, the number
of attempts on a problem.
Maybe you want to change the specific terminology
or replace a link in a bunch of your HTML components.
How do you do this?
Well, the easiest way to do this is to download your course,
unzip it, and process it either in Python
or even a text editor with a multi file Find and Replace feature, and then
re-zip it and put it back up on your platform.
Why would you want to do something so crazy?
Playing with XML is very, very dangerous.
The reason you want to do this is because you often
need to do things within a deadline.
So somebody has to make sure that this course has this change
and you've got three days to do it.
Three days is probably just enough time to manage 160 videos in a course
and make them all downloadable and make sure all your work is done correctly.
However, using this batched process method,
you can actually do this within five minutes.
It saves you a tremendous amount of time.
The other reason why you might want to do this is an organizational change.
So say procedures have changed.
We're changing the IP rules around our property.
Making a video downloadable or not downloadable
is something that you can also do.
Just go and find the variable that you would like to modify
and make sure you replace the term that you need.