Amy: Automatic allocation for cohorts is pretty straightforward.
First, go to the Instructor Dashboard in the Live view of your course.
Then click Cohorts, and tick the Enable Cohorts button.
This brings up a new button prompting to add cohorts.
Now, in this example, we know we want to make
three cohorts named A, B, and C. So let's start with cohort A.
We know we want users to be automatically allocated
so that when people join the course, they're randomly assigned to a cohort.
And we know we don't need any specific content to be displayed.
Once happy with the settings, press Submit.
Then repeat until all cohorts are set up.
Remember, once a name is used for your cohort, you can't change or delete it.
So make sure you are happy with everything on this page
before you press Submit.
As these are automatic allocations, for as long as this box is ticked,
users will be assigned to a cohort the minute the course goes live
and they access the site.
If you change your mind on cohorts before the course goes live,
you can always come back to this button and untick the selection.
At this stage, you're now ready to go.
Now, hypothetically, if we were to need specific cohort views or experiment
group configurations for research purposes, you can tick here,
and it will take you to Group Configurations in Studio.
You can also access this via Settings then Group Configuration in Studio
on the top navigation bar.
Finally, if you were to need to change a user's cohort allocation at any time,
you can simply select the Required New Cohort from the dropdown
and add the user's email address in the box below.
This will override any previous allocation, however, and
is pretty risky if the course is already live, as their previous submissions may
be affected.