ANDREW ANG: Hi, I'm Andrew Ang.
I'm a data engineer with Harvard's Vise Provost
for Advances and Learning Research group, where
we harness data to research and improve the educational experience, both online
and here on campus.
One particular area of interest for us is adaptive and personalized learning.
Online courses offer an unprecedented opportunity
to reach learners all over the world at scale.
To reach learners that may not have the opportunity
given their location or circumstances.
Our research has shown that learners in online courses
come from all walks of life, with different backgrounds, ages, education
levels, domain experience, and come with different motivations and goals
for what they want to get out of the course.
It's hard to imagine a one size fits all approach being optimal
for every single one of these diverse learners.
That's where adaptivity can help.
So what exactly do we mean by adaptivity?
There in a lot of ways that a learning experience can be adaptive.
For example, instead of a typical quiz where every learner sees the same 10
questions, imagine a quiz where learners instead see one question at a time.
They have to answer the previous question
before moving on to the next one.
We customize the topic and difficulty of the question they see next
based on their previous answers.
Each learner will get a different sequence
of questions that is exactly tailored to their particular needs.
The idea is to constantly measure the student's knowledge
levels of each topic and to serve them questions in a smart way,
with the goal of maximizing the students' knowledge
level for all of those relevant topics that we are tracking.
That sounds idealistic, but it is actually quite possible
to integrate into your ethics course.
Here are some things to think about before embarking on this approach.
First, you have to define a set of topics, or as we call them,
knowledge components, that your course materials address.
Second, you'll have to develop a lot more material in order
for an adaptive system to address the needs of particular learners.
It has to have a large collection of differentiated materials
that adaptive system can choose from.
Third, you have to tag each individual piece
of material with one or more knowledge components, and ideally, difficulty
as well.
Finally, the edX platform doesn't support
this kind of functionality natively, so you'll
need to install a tool like the open source
system we've developed to handle the contents, metadata, Knowledge
Tracing, and the user interface.
It's a lot of work.
You'll need to decide whether it's worth the payoff of offering
a more engaging and personalized learning experience for your learners.