<problem display_name="Out of Order" markdown="null" max_attempts="2" showanswer="finished">
  <multiplechoiceresponse>
    <p>You're having trouble with your walkthrough: it's showing things in the wrong order. Here's what the code looks like:</p>
    <pre>
      <code class="lang-js">    let courseware = $('.course-tabs .active');
    courseware.attr("data-step", "1");
    courseware.attr("data-intro", "The course outline, including pages with all the videos, problems, and more, can all be found in the Course link.");
    courseware.attr("data-position", "right")

    let progress = $('.course-tabs').find('a:contains("Progress")');
    progress.attr("data-step", "3");
    progress.attr("data-intro", "The Progress tab is where you can find your grade.");
    progress.attr("data-position", "right");
  
    let discussion = $('.course-tabs').find('a:contains("Discussion")');
    discussion.attr("data-step", "2");
    discussion.attr("data-intro", "The Discussion link sends you to the discussion boards, where you can talk to your fellow students.");
    discussion.attr("data-position", "right");

    let syllabus = $('.course-tabs').find('a:contains("Syllabus")');
    syllabus.attr("data-step", "4");
    syllabus.attr("data-intro", "The Syllabus tab will tell you about the course contents and policies. You will want to read this early.");
    syllabus.attr("data-position", "right");
</code>
    </pre>
    <br/>
    <p>You want the walkthrough to start with the Course tab, then go to Progress, Discussion, and Syllabus, in that order.</p>
    <label>What is wrong with this code?</label>
    <description>If you see more than one thing wrong, pick the easiest thing to fix.</description>
    <choicegroup shuffle="true" type="MultipleChoice">
      <choice correct="false">The middle two blocks are in the wrong order.</choice>
      <choice correct="true">The data-step attribute is out of order.</choice>
      <choice correct="false">The jQuery selector is picking the wrong thing.</choice>
      <choice correct="false">There is a line missing a semicolon.</choice>
    </choicegroup>
  </multiplechoiceresponse>
  <solution>
    <div class="detailed-solution">
      <p>Explanation</p>
      <p>The easiest fix here is to change the data-step, which tells the walkthrough what order things are in. Changing the order of the code blocks doesn't change what order the walkthrough uses.</p>
      <p>There is indeed a line without a semicolon, but javascript is particularly (perhaps "notoriously") permissive when it comes to missing semicolons and will likely run just fine without it.</p>
    </div>
  </solution>
</problem>
